Finding Aid for University at Buffalo Music Department Oral History Recordings, 1980-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1980-1996, I.; Cassette 1-61
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-12-07, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 7 Dec. 1991 Sides 1 and 2 Duration: 01:03:32 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 45)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_45_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_45_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_45_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_45_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-12-07, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 7 Dec. 1991 Sides 3 and 4 Duration: 01:36:24 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: JVC GI-90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 46)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_46_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_46_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_46_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_46_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-12-07, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 7 Dec. 1991 Sides 5 and 6 Duration: 00:33:48 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 47)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_47_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_47_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_47_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_47_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-12-08, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 8 December 1991 Sides 1 and 2 Duration: 01:21:34 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: JVC GI-90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 2, Audiocassette 48)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_48_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_48_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_48_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_48_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-12-08, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 8 December 1991 Sides 3 and 4 Duration: 01:38:09 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: Maxell XLII 100 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 2, Audiocassette 49)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_49_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_49_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_49_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_49_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-12-14, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 14 December 1991 Sides 1 and 2 Duration: 01:44:44 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: Maxell XLII 100 stereo. Side 3 of this interview is on Tape 44 Side B; Marked Dub (Box 2, Audiocassette 50)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_50_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_50_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_50_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_50_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1994-04-03, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 3 April 1994 Duration: 00:22:11 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. Marked Dub. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 51)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_51_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_51_01_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1981-10-27, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Mr. Allen Sigel 10/27/81 Duration: 00:29:26 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 52)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_52_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_52_01_sc.mp3
  - Slatin, Myles, 1994-01-17, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Myles Slatin 17 January 1994 Duration: 00:52:40 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: Maxell XLII 90 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 53)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_53_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_53_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_53_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_53_02_sc.mp3
  - Smit, Leo, 1921-1999, 1981-11-19, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Mr. Leo Smit 11/19/81 Duration: 00:26:30 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 54)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_54_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_54_01_sc.mp3
  - Tinney, Al, 1980-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Music 515 class directed by James Patrick Spine title: Tinney, Allen #1 Duration: 00:59:39 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 55)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_55_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_55_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_55_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_55_02_sc.mp3
  - Tinney, Al, 1980-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Music 515 class directed by James Patrick Spine title: Tinney, Allen #2 Duration: 01:02:25 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 56)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_56_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_56_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_56_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_56_02_sc.mp3
  - Tinney, Al, 1980-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Music 515 class directed by James Patrick Spine title: Tinney, Allen #3 Duration: 00:36:34 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 57)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_57_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_57_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_57_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_57_02_sc.mp3
  - Turner, Hazel, 1980-02-21, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Vine, Rita Spine title: Turner, Hazel Feb. 21 1980 Duration: 01:11:59 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C90 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 58)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_58_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_58_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_58_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_58_02_sc.mp3
  - Van Arsdale, Jane, 1980-01-10, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Vine, Rita Spine title: Van Arsdale, Jane Tape #1 Duration: 00:57:10 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 59)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_59_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_59_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_59_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_59_02_sc.mp3
  - Van Arsdale, Jane, 1980-01-10, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Vine, Rita Spine title: Van Arsdale, Jane Tape #2 Duration: 00:08:27 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 60)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_60_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_60_01_sc.mp3
  - Williams, Jan, 1939-, 1993-02-17, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Jan Williams 17 Feb. 93 Duration: 00:39:39 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: Maxell XLII 90 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 61)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_61_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_61_01_sc.mp3
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
Almquist, Sharon G.; Bradley, Carol June; Green, Alan, 1962-; Steinzor, Curt Efram; Vine, Rita
Subjects
Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999; Tinney, Al; Cornelissen, Arnold; Gearhart, Livingston; Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009; State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Department; State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library; Music librarians--Interviews; Music -- New York (State) -- Buffalo -- History; Music -- Instruction and study -- New York (State) -- Buffalo -- History
Genres
audiocassettes; oral histories (document genres)